Employee Payroll App Documentation

General Instructions:
    1. Run program by entering: 'dot net run' in console and press 'Enter'.
    2. Once Welcome message is displayed press 'Enter'.
    3. Follow the Instructions indicated to access the app features.

Features:
1. Create / Add New Employee
    - Input employee details based on the required field displayed then press 'Enter' to proceed to the next required field.
    1.1 Salary details
        - User should input monthly pay for both:
            - Taxable Pay : Will be used in tax calculation
            - Non-Taxable Pay : Exempted from tax calculation
    1.2 Tax details
        1.2.1 Taxes are predefined to the following additional taxes should be added in Other Taxes.
            - Income Tax
            - Social Security
            - Health Insurance
            - Other Taxes*
        1.2.2 User is prompted to choose between manual and automatic tax calculation
            - Manual : Tax rates are then required to be manually input by the user
            - Automatic : Tax rates are based on the government (sample)
2. Read/Display
    - Display employee payslip in a predefined format
    2.1 Display single employee payslip
        - User should input Employee ID of the desired employee payslip to view
        - App will prompt user to view another payslip
    2.2 View all employee payslip
        - Display all employee payslips
3. Update/Modify
    - Update includes employee, income and salary details. User should input employee ID to update and select which details to update.
    3.1 Employee details
        - Update employee details including name, status, position, etc.
    3.2 Salary details
        - When updating salary details, taxes will be recalculated.
        User will be prompted if taxes should be calculated manually or automatically (see 1.2.2)
    3.3 Tax details
        - Since predefined taxes are calculated only other taxes will be allowed to be updated.
4. Delete Employee
    - User should input Employee ID of the employee to be deleted.

App Limitations:
    1. Exception Handling : Most exceptions are handled with the proper message but will end the application.
                            User should rerun the application to perform another action.
    2. Tax Limitations : Taxes are predefined therefore other employee taxes should be added under Other Taxes
    3. Income Limitation : Similar to taxes, income are predefined to taxable and non-taxable only.
